Well, I thought I'd go cycling today.
うかた、今日はサイクリングをしようかなと思って
Oh, nice.
ああ、いいね
You can rent a bicycle now,
今から自転車をレンタルできるから、
Let's borrow it and change things up a bit.
それ借りて、ちょっと気分転換しよう
Yeah, let's do that.
うん、そうしよう
Isn't the weather nice?
天気良くない?
The weather is nice.
天気良いね
That's really good.
めっちゃ良いね
Cycling view ring.
サイクリングビューリング
that's why.
だから
Wow, the scenery is so beautiful.
すごい、景色めっちゃ綺麗
Hey, the flowers are blooming too.
ねえ、お花も咲いてるし
Hey.
ね え
You can see the sea.
海見えるじゃん
beautiful.
綺麗
It's true.
本当だ
Let's stop clinking for once.
一回、チャリンコ止めよう
This can go even higher.
これ、上とかも行けるんだね
Shall we go up?
上行ってみる?
Yeah, let's go.
うん、行こう
Observation corner.
展望コーナー
cool.
涼しい
It's cool.
涼しいね
That flower is amazing.
あっち花すご
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
Isn't it dangerous?
ヤバくない?
That's dangerous.
ヤバい
I'd like to go there too.
あっちも行ってみたいね
Hey.
ねえ
How do I get there?
どうやって行くんだろう?
Let's go for a walk later.
あとでちょっと歩いて行ってみよう
Seriously, this place is beautiful.
マジでここが綺麗
It's crazy here.
ここヤバいね
That's dangerous.
ヤバい
jet skil.
ジェットスキール
Hey, I want to do it.
おい、やりたい
It's quite active.
結構アクティブだね
I guess I'll do pretty much anything.
割と何でもするかな
Aoi-chan, do you like exercise?
あおいちゃん運動好きなの?
I just went surfing the other day.
この間サーフィンもしてきたばっか
Seriously?
マジで?
Yeah.
うん
Can you also surf?
サーフィンもできるの?
It can be done.
出来ます
amazing.
すごい
I also play Sunnobo.
スンノボもするし
Do you like sea sports?
海のスポーツ結構好き?
But I would like to have a summit meeting next time.
でも今度首脳ケリングをしたい
I want to go to the beach with you once we get a little better friends.
俺 はちょっと仲良くなったら海一緒に行きたいな
It looks like he's actually wearing it.
実質着てるようだ
I agree.
そうだね
Good thing I brought saltwater pants.
海水パンツ持ってくれよかった
The sea certainly looks nice today.
確かに今日の海気持ちよさそう
It feels really good.
めっちゃ気持ちいいよね
I love the sea, but my skin is pale.
海好きなのに肌白いよね
It doesn't burn.
焼けない
Can't you bake it?
焼けないの?
First, whitening girls.
まず美白女子
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
But I didn't think Aoi-chan was into sports that much.
でもあおいちゃんがそんなにスポーツやってると思わなかった
He was extremely active.
めちゃくちゃアクティブだった
What about your school friends?
学校の友達とかは?
Vocational school.
専門学校
Well, I guess there aren't that many children.
えー、ある子でも少ないんじゃないかな
I feel like everyone is worried about sunburn.
みんな日焼けとか気にしてる気がする
I can do it because it doesn't burn.
焼けないから出来るけど
It seems like all girls these days don't like it unless their skin is fair.
最近の女子ってみんなさ、肌白くないと嫌だみたいな
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じだよね
hey.
ね
Looks delicious.
美味そうだね
It looked really delicious.
めっちゃ美味しそうだった
Shall I buy it for you later?
あとで買ってあげよっか
Is it okay?
いいの?
What do you want to eat?
何食べたいの?
Oh, the ice cream looks delicious.
え、アイスが美味しそう
Do you want to eat ice cream?
アイス食べたい?
Yeah.
うん
This skin is cute.
この肌可愛い
which one?
どれ?
W-what is this?
わ、なにこれ?
Haven't you seen it?
見たことない?
Huh, does it suit you?
え、似合う?
Oh, it really, really suits you.
え、めっちゃ、めっちゃ似合う
What do you say?
何言わんの?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
It suits you.
似合う
Did you have fun in high school?
高校の時って楽しかった?
Well, I guess it was fun.
まあ、楽しかったかな
Did you continue to participate in club activities for three years?
部活も3年間続けたの?
In high school, I didn't have any club activities.
高校はね、部活してなかった
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Yeah, I went to the gym.
うん、ジム通ってた
Oh, do you also exercise?
あ、運動もしてるの?
Yeah.
うん
I've stopped it now though.
今、やめちゃったけど
Well then, we're gym buddies.
じゃあ、僕たちジム仲間だね
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you go to the gym?
ジ ム通ってるの?
I go there.
通ってるよ
Well, there's a pool at the gym.
なんか、ジムにプールがあるから
Pool?
プール?
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
You said you were swimming.
水泳やってるって言ったもんね
I've been swimming for 6 years.
水泳、6年間ずっとやってたから
Seriously?
まじか
I don't even tan.
日焼きもしないし
Aoi-chan swimming,
葵ちゃんが水泳で泳いでるところ、
I want to follow you, crawl.
後ろからついてきたいな、クロール
Crawl.
クロールかい
Yeah, I'd like to see you swimming.
うん、水泳姿、ちょっと見てみたいな
Oh, you can bring your pets here too.
あ、ここペットもいっけよ
Eh, amazing.
えー、すごい
I guess it's because there are so many people walking around.
やっぱ散歩する人が多いからかな
Ah, it's cool.
あ、涼しい
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
Ah, the wind is just right.
あ、風がちょうどいい
The wind is just right.
風ちょうどいいね
Good.
よいしょ
copper?
どう?
delicious.
おいしい
Wow, that's refreshing.
すごい、爽快か
Ah, the slope feels good.
あ、坂気持ちいい
The slope feels good.
坂気持ちいいね
Quite early.
結構早い
It's early.
早いね
I'm really happy.
まじで嬉しい
At first, I said that I was so scared of bicycles.
最初はあんだけ自転車怖い怖い言ってたのにさ
Well, besides, I'm having fun right now.
ね え、それに今楽しいんだけど
It's fun though.
楽しいんだけどね
Once you get up here, you're already at the boarding point.
ここ登ったらもう乗り場だね
Hey.
ねえ
Thank you for riding the Flower Ferris Wheel.
花の大観覧車にご乗車いただきまして
Thank you very much.
誠にありがとうございます
Sister.
お姉ちゃん
Yeah.
うん
Thank you for your understanding.
ご乗車に際しまして
When riding Fairis Wheel, do not close Gandara or the door.
フェアリスウィールを乗る際は、 ガンダラやドアを閉じないで
please.
ください
Sister, let me see.
お 姉ちゃん、ちょっと見せて
why?
なんで?
picture?
え?
Sister.
お姉ちゃん
Isn't this beautiful too?
こっちも綺麗なんじゃない?
Hey.
ねえ
picture?
え?
No?
だめ?
No.
だめだよ
why?
なんで?
That's not what it is.
そういうのじゃないじゃん
Well, that's true, but today...
いや、そりゃそうだけど、 今日さ、
I was wondering if there was one version.
ワンチャンありなのかなって思ってた
No.
違うよ
Is it different?
違うの?
No.
違うよ
Hey, I might not be able to hold back.
ねえ、俺結構我慢できないかもしれない
Stop it.
やめて
Seriously.
まじで
Stop it.
やめて
why?
なん で?
なんで?
No, really.
いや、本当に
why?
なんで?
Really stop it.
本当にやめて
Seriously?
まじで?
Yeah.
うん
Then,
そしたらさ、
It's okay if you lick mine.
俺 の舐めるんだったらいい
Hmm.
うーん
picture?
え?
Awesome.
すげえ
What happened?
どうなってきた?
Chin chin.
ち んちん
Are you starting to understand?
わかってなってきた?
oh yeah.
そうそう
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
At this aquarium, from the Ministry of Postpartum of Netari,
この水族園には、 ネッタリの産後省から、
Covered by Bowlin, from the North Pole to the South Pole,
ボウリンを覆われた、 北極、南極に至る、
It is home to sea creatures from all over the world.
世界の海の生き物たちが生息しています
Before going to bed, Edogawa Ward recommends:
水 族園より寝前には、 江 戸川区がお勧めする、
Tropical Pole Leafs,
ト ロフィカル・ポール・リーフス、
Ice Cap Arctic, Ant Arctic,
アイスキャップ・アークティク、 アントアクティク、
Before going to bed at the aquarium, Edogawa Ward recommends:
水族園より寝前には、 江戸川区がお勧めする、
You can see Hotel Seaside Edogawa.
ホテルシーサイド江戸川がご覧いただけます
As a base for traveling not only to Tokoen but also to the surrounding area,
東光園はもとより、 周辺への移動の拠点に、
Many households use it.
多くの家庭が利用されています
In front of the overseas park is Hotel Seaside Edogawa.
海外のパークの前に、 ホテルシーサイド江戸川があります
It operates in Edogawa Bay.
江戸川湾で運営されています
Many people use Hotel Seaside.
多くの人はホテルシーサイドを使用しています
Exploring the park and surrounding areas.
パークや周辺の地域を探検しています
Further south, there are buildings that are closed from the front,
さらに南側には、 前面から締まりの建物、
Full view rest house,
全貌レストハウス、
The competition course of the Tokyo 2020 Olympics, looking east,
東 京2020オリンピックの 東向に見える競技コースが、
The course is approximately 400 meters long, and passes through a gate set in the middle of the course.
長さ約400メートルあり、 コース途中に設置されたゲートを通
A competition in which people compete for the time and skill to descend to the finish line while
過 しながら、 フィニッシュまで下る時間や技術を競う競技
is.
です
The course on the left is about 200 meters long.
左 側 の コースは約200メートル長いです
The time and technique required to descend to the finish while passing through the competition course.
競 技コースを通過しながら、 フィニッシュまで下る時間や技術
compete for
を 競う
It's a competition.
競 技です
Moreover, in the middle of the night,
さ ら に、夜中には、
You can see a beautiful view of the light coming from the water.
水 面からの光の美しい景色を見ることができます
On the west side, there is the Arakawa rock big tree accumulation area,
西側には、 荒川の岩の大木集積場、
A car station on the People's Expressway Wangan Line, and the JR Keiyo Line that connects Tokyo and Chiba.
人高速湾岸線の自動車の駅、 そして東京と千葉を結ぶJR慶養線
You can see the Tsuryu Seki Line.
と、 津流の関線がご覧いただけます
To the west is the main Logistic World...
西側には、 メイン・ロジスティック・ワールド...
During the story, I felt really good.
話の中で、 すっげぇ気持ちよかった
Look at Aoi-chan's white bunaji from above.
上から見ててさ、 アオイちゃんの白いブナジとかさ、
I reacted a lot.
めっちゃ反応しちゃって
Karlin-san, can I make you feel good?
カーリンさん、 気持ちよくさせていい?
About Aoi-chan.
アオイちゃんのこと
Are you called “Seroshiroi”?
せろしろいって言われる?
Yes, it is said.
うん、言われる
I'm sweating so much that I'm dripping down here.
ここに垂れるぐらい汗ついてる
Because it was hot.
暑かったから
I love anime.
アニメ好き
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
together?
一緒?
Yeah, together.
うん、一緒
together?
一緒?
the garment
その衣
The outfit.
装 が
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Always use that voice.
いつもそれの声をつけてね
Hands, below.
手、下で
It's moist.
しっとりしてる
keep it moist
しっとりして
Ru.
る
Sweat It's also really beautiful.
汗 なんかもすげぇ綺麗
It's not in there.
入ってないよ
Do you always smoke?
いつも吸ってる?
Yeah.
うん
But I just shaved it.
でもこれ剃ったばっかじゃん
So beautiful.
すげぇ綺麗
So today, I said at the beginning that I didn't like it, but
じゃあ今日、 最初の中で嫌って言ってたけど、
It might have an impact.
影響あるかも
Okay.
いいよ
Hair is removed.
脱毛されてる
Has your hair been removed?
脱毛されてるか
amazing.
すごい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Where is the girl with beautiful skin?
肌きれいな子はどこ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
nostalgic?
懐かしい?
What do you feel the most here?
ここ一番感じる?
Yeah.
うん
Which one do you like?
ど っちが好き?
Is it early?
早いの?
I prefer early.
早いほうが好き
I've been filling it up gradually.
だんだん充填してきた
The pink area is filling up.
ピンクのここが充填してきた
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
You licked 6, 7, 8, 7 a lot, right?
6、7、8、7いっぱい舐めたでしょ?
If you impressed me, you probably gave me a good lick, didn't you?
感激させてくれたら多分、 しっかり舐めたじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I'm looking at your head.
頭見てる
Can you take it off here?
こっちに脱がせられる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Take it off.
脱いで
It's extremely difficult.
めちゃくちゃ難しい
It's similar to Kainash from earlier.
さっきのカイナッシュと同じようなんですよ
I'm licking it anyway.
どうせ舐めてる
Oh dear, just like you did with Kainash earlier.
あうちゃんさ、さっきカイナッシュでしたみたいに
Look at me while licking it.
ペラペラ舐めながらこっち見て
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い
Don't be shy.
恥ずかしがらないで
Look from the side.
横で見て
Ai-chan, is it hard to lick while sitting sideways?
あうちゃん、横座りで舐めずらい?
Yeah.
うん
Ai-chan, just fell asleep.
あうちゃん、さっき寝て
It's so cute while licking it properly.
しっかり舐めながら、めっちゃ可愛い
Is it different while licking like this?
こんな舐めながら違う?
Yeah, that's not it.
うん、違う
What should I do?
どうする?
on the shoulder.
肩に
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
A-chan, it's really warm inside.
あ うちゃん、中めっちゃ温かい
It's nice and warm.
すっぽく温かい
Will it get hard?
固くなってくるの?
I know.
知ってるんだ
Also, the penis becomes harder.
それもちんちんの方が固くなってくる
Oh-chan, middle, middle, middle.
あうちゃん、中、中、中
Can you move it yourself?
自分で動かせる?
Yeah, it feels good.
うん、気持ちいい
Hit right?
右打ち当たる?
Yeah.
うん
bean paste
あん
Isn't it?
ま ないかな?
Oh-chan, you like this one better, right?
あうちゃん、こっちの方が好きでしょ?
It hits all the entrances.
入り口いっぱい当たる
yes?
そう?
what?
何?
Oh-chan, what's wrong?
あうちゃん、どうしたの?
Shall we go home?
帰ろうかな?
Isn't it early?
早くない?
Is there not?
ないかな?
It was really fun.
めっちゃ楽しかったね
Shall we go home?
帰ろうかな?
Anyway, please take your time as usual.
なんでも、いつもしかゆっくりしてこいですけどね
Yeah, I see.
うん、なるほど
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
real?
ほんと?
Maybe it's really dry.
すっげぇドライなのかも
That's what I was saying earlier.
さっきめっちゃ言ってたの
good.
よかった
Will the broadcast be found out?
配信バレない?
Yeah, I won't find out.
うん、バレないよ
What if I find out?
もしバレたらどうすんの?
oh dear...
まあ...
I even thought about it.
思いもしたって
good?
いい?
How do you like it?
いかがか?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫だっけ?
Yeah.
うん
Did you try to go home like this?
こんな感じで帰ろうとしたの?
Yeah.
うん
It's early tomorrow morning too.
明日も朝早いし
Huh, has it stopped?
え、止まってきてんの?
picture?
え?
I just went to the big one.
さっき大きい中ついたの
yeah?
ん?
Since it was large, it remains in that shape.
大きいついたから、その形のまま残ってる
Can't you see inside?
奥見えんの?
a
あ
N-chan?
ん ちゃん?
Yeah?
うん?
Sit on my face.
顔上に座って
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Let's try making it a little stronger.
もう少し強くしてみようか
Yeah.
うん
What, are you going?
え、行くの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm going outside.
外に行っちゃう
It looks like I can go as far as going outside.
外行くまで行けるみたいな
Shall we go?
行そう?
Which one did you go with?
どっちと行ったの?
Did you go outside?
外で行ったの?
Which one will it be?
どっちになる?
I won't go.
行かない
yeah?
ん?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Is the entrance completely empty?
入り口めちゃくちゃ空いてる?
Yeah.
うん